### **N**AY **W**ILKINS

Austin, TX 78745 | Phone: 479-409-0876 | Email: nathanwilkins01@gmail.com LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/naywilkins/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/naywilkins/</a> | GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/naywilkins512">https://github.com/naywilkins512</a> Portfolio: <a href="https://naywilkins512.github.io/Portfolio/">https://naywilkins512.github.io/Portfolio/</a>

#### SUMMARY

MERN-Stack Developer with a specialty in utilizing front-end design to communicate clients' missions. A decade of managing, directing, and booking a full-staff music venue & touring the world as a composer, known for adapting with constantly changing environments and meeting every task with optimism and excitement.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, JavaScript, PHP, CSS, GSAP, Scrolltrigger, Tone.JS,

Applications: Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Premiere, Adobe AfterEffects, Figma, Slack, Canva

#### EXPERIENCE

# **She Shreds Media**; Portland, OR *Full Stack Web Developer*

2020 - Present

Work closely with the CEO and Designer to create weekly online experiences for musicians, with a focus on women artists.

- Created the webpage which connected over 1,000 musicians globally in the span of a month.
- Helped launch the first She Shreds livestream open mic event.

# Quack's Bakery, LLC; Austin, TX Web Developer (2019 – Present)

2016 - Present

Full Stack web developer working closely with the CEO and Designer to create a website for a regional bakery.

Designed and coded the website including forms for Wholesale and Event Booking.

#### **Event Coordinator & Social Media Management** (2016 – Present)

Manage 3 storefront's live event booking, negotiate artist payments, facilitate show promotion, create content, and manage social media accounts.

#### **P**ROJECTS

#### 1RAD.WORLD | https://sheshreds.com/1rad-2021-home/

- A website for connecting musicians globally featuring a live stream of #1rad hashtagged Instagram posts, music tutorials, a weekly zoom open mic, and a forum.
- Role: Created a four page website in collaboration with the Designer.
- Tools: Wordpress, PHP, CSS, Zoom

# **Texas Parks Rebrand** | https://github.com/naywilkins512/Parks\_n\_Req | https://salty-hamlet-73070.herokuapp.com/

- This app was a re-imagination of the camping reservation/park information application currently used by the Texas State Parks reservation system.
- Role: Created the landing page, GSAP Scrolltrigger Animation, and Image Mapping.
- Tools: Javascript, Scrolltrigger, GSAP, CSS

#### InBloom | https://github.com/naywilkins512/inBloom | https://in-bloom.herokuapp.com/

- A web application utilizing the MERN stack, created to allow the user a platform to easily track their care instructions for their plants.
- Role: Created the homepage and GSAP animation.
- Tools: Javascript, CSS, GSAP, Adobe Illustrator

#### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web Development Certificate: University Of Texas, Austin, TX | 2020